(Raj:)So, I did a little
research on what
(Raj:)the conditions are like
in the mines,
(Raj:)and the guys might be right--
(Raj:)sounds pretty rough
down there.
(Raj:)For starters, it's very humid,
(Raj:)and about a hundred degrees.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm from Texas
and you're from India--
(Sheldon:)we're no strangers
to the fragrant armpit. Next.
(Raj:)It's also a live mine, so
there'll be dynamite explosions
(Raj:)going off in the distance.
Yeah, I have
a lactose-intolerant roommate
(Sheldon:)with a taste
for ice cream. Next.
(Raj:)Oh, you have to be down there
for 12 hours at a time.
(Sheldon:)Yeah? We have to be somewhere.
(Raj:)Well, there's no toilets--
(Raj:)we'll have to do our business
in a bucket.
(Sheldon:)So it's settled--
we're not doing it.
(Raj:)Look, I get it, but...
before we pass up
(Raj:)on an incredible opportunity,
I was thinking about
(Raj:)when Howard was training
to go to space,
(Raj:)they put him
in a simulated environment.
(Sheldon:)Interesting. You're
suggesting that we recreate
(Raj:)the conditions
of the mine
(Sheldon:)to see if we
can handle it.
Exactly.